englishfiles.com 2004-12-13

# Privacy Statement for EnglishLearner.com

## Privacy Statement for EnglishLearner.com

EnglishLearner.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: EnglishLearner.com.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **EnglishLearner.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site.

EnglishLearner.com works with third parties that serve ads to this site.  

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [ElekMathe@EnglishLearner.com](mailto:elekmathe@englishlearner.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: <http://www.englishlearner.com/online/problems.html>

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [ElekMathe@EnglishLearner.com](mailto:elekmathe@englishlearner.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Elek Mathe EnglishLearner.com ElekMathe@EnglishLearner.com
